[{"Answers": ["1945", "1943", "1940"], "Correct": "1939", "Question": "'World War II ( ____ 1945) was the largest armed conflict in human history."}, {"Answers": ["59", "57", "60"], "Correct": "50", "Question": "Ranging over six continents and all the world's oceans, the war caused an estimated  ____ million military and civilian deaths, including those of 6 million Jews."}, {"Answers": ["1950", "1941", "1942"], "Correct": "1939", "Question": "Although the war began with Nazi Germany's attack on Poland in September  ____  the United States did not enter the war until after the Japanese bombed the American fleet in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, on December 7, 1941."}, {"Answers": ["1942", "1946", "1949"], "Correct": "1939", "Question": "In November  ____  he persuaded Congress to repeal the arms embargo provisions of the neutrality law so that arms could be sold to France and Britain."}, {"Answers": ["1950", "1945", "1951"], "Correct": "1940", "Question": "After the fall of France in the spring of June  ____  he pushed for a major military buildup and began providing aid in the form of Lend-Lease to Britain, which now stood alone against the Axis powers."}, {"Answers": ["1950", "1947", "1949"], "Correct": "1941", "Question": "From then on, America's capacity to produce hundreds of thousands of tanks, airplanes, and ships for itself and its allies proved a crucial factor in Allied success, as did the fierce resistance of the Soviet Union, which had joined the war in June  ____ after being attacked by Germany."}, {"Answers": ["1945", "1946", "1947"], "Correct": "1942", "Question": "Among the war's major turning points for the United States were the Battle of Midway ( ____ , the invasion of Italy (1943), the Allied invasion of France (1944), the battle of Leyte Gulf (1944) and the dropping of the atomic bombs on Japan (1945)."}, {"Answers": ["1954", "1947", "1955"], "Correct": "1945", "Question": "The war ended with the Axis powers' unconditional surrender in  ____ "}, {"Answers": ["1943", "1951", "1947"], "Correct": "1942", "Question": "At FDR's behest she undertook two major tours, one to Europe ( ____  and one to the South Pacific (1943), where she met with Allied servicemen and wartime leaders, providing comfort and boosting morale."}, {"Answers": ["1949", "1948", "1951"], "Correct": "1941", "Question": "Together with NAACP Executive Secretary Walter White and African American union leader A. Philip Randolph, she persuaded Franklin D. Roosevelt to issue an executive order in  ____ prohibiting racial discrimination in defense industries and establishing the Fair Employment Practices Commission."}, {"Answers": ["1949", "1940", "1944"], "Correct": "1939", "Question": "'World War II ( ____ 1945) was the largest armed conflict in human history."}, {"Answers": ["56", "59", "58"], "Correct": "50", "Question": "Ranging over six continents and all the world's oceans, the war caused an estimated  ____ million military and civilian deaths, including those of 6 million Jews."}, {"Answers": ["1947", "1948", "1949"], "Correct": "1939", "Question": "Although the war began with Nazi Germany's attack on Poland in September  ____  the United States did not enter the war until after the Japanese bombed the American fleet in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, on December 7, 1941."}, {"Answers": ["1943", "1940", "1941"], "Correct": "1939", "Question": "In November  ____  he persuaded Congress to repeal the arms embargo provisions of the neutrality law so that arms could be sold to France and Britain."}, {"Answers": ["1947", "1941", "1951"], "Correct": "1940", "Question": "After the fall of France in the spring of June  ____  he pushed for a major military buildup and began providing aid in the form of Lend-Lease to Britain, which now stood alone against the Axis powers."}, {"Answers": ["1948", "1942", "1944"], "Correct": "1941", "Question": "From then on, America's capacity to produce hundreds of thousands of tanks, airplanes, and ships for itself and its allies proved a crucial factor in Allied success, as did the fierce resistance of the Soviet Union, which had joined the war in June  ____ after being attacked by Germany."}, {"Answers": ["1947", "1952", "1953"], "Correct": "1942", "Question": "Among the war's major turning points for the United States were the Battle of Midway ( ____ , the invasion of Italy (1943), the Allied invasion of France (1944), the battle of Leyte Gulf (1944) and the dropping of the atomic bombs on Japan (1945)."}, {"Answers": ["1954", "1949", "1951"], "Correct": "1945", "Question": "The war ended with the Axis powers' unconditional surrender in  ____ "}, {"Answers": ["1944", "1951", "1946"], "Correct": "1942", "Question": "At FDR's behest she undertook two major tours, one to Europe ( ____  and one to the South Pacific (1943), where she met with Allied servicemen and wartime leaders, providing comfort and boosting morale."}, {"Answers": ["1948", "1947", "1942"], "Correct": "1941", "Question": "Together with NAACP Executive Secretary Walter White and African American union leader A. Philip Randolph, she persuaded Franklin D. Roosevelt to issue an executive order in  ____ prohibiting racial discrimination in defense industries and establishing the Fair Employment Practices Commission."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "World War II", "Question": "Global in scale and in its repercussions,  ____ created a new world at home and abroad."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "United Nations", "Question": "The war also ended America's relative isolation from the rest of the world and resulted in the creation of the  ____ "}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "Great Depression", "Question": "Domestically, the war ended the  ____ as hundreds of thousands of people, many of them women, went into the defense industries."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "United States", "Question": "The roots of World War II, which eventually pitted Germany, Japan, and Italy (the Axis) against the  ____  Great Britain and the Soviet Union (the Allies), lay in the militaristic ideologies and expansionist policies of Nazi Germany, Italy, and Japan."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "Soviet Union", "Question": "From then on, America's capacity to produce hundreds of thousands of tanks, airplanes, and ships for itself and its allies proved a crucial factor in Allied success, as did the fierce resistance of the  ____  which had joined the war in June 1941 after being attacked by Germany."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "Dwight D. Eisenhower", "Question": "The brilliance of America's military leaders, including General  ____  who planned and led the attack against the Nazis in Western Europe, and General Douglas MacArthur and Fleet Admiral Chester Nimitz, who led the Allied effort in the Pacific, also contributed to the Allied victory."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "United States", "Question": "Among the war's major turning points for the  ____ were the Battle of Midway (1942), the invasion of Italy (1943), the Allied invasion of France (1944), the battle of Leyte Gulf (1944) and the dropping of the atomic bombs on Japan (1945)."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "war", "Question": "Her efforts were often frustrated, but she did not give up and continued to pursue this work after the  ____ when it was easier for refugees to leave Europe."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "My Day", "Question": "On the home front, she visited defense plants around the country and used her  ____ column and speeches to encourage the war effort."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "ER", "Question": "After the war,  ____ supported the right of women to remain in their jobs if they depended on their wages."}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "Free Response - Location", "Question": "What happened in the United States?"}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "Free Response - Event", "Question": "What happened during the World War II?"}, {"Answers": [" ", " ", " "], "Correct": "Free Response - Person", "Question": "What is the importance of Dwight D. Eisenhower?"}]